[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["next week"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "PERCENT": ["20 percent"]}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "CD", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "POS", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "WRB", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Is it a real possibility?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Well, it now -- Real Clear Politics, it's up to 20 percent when it was down in single digits before, and it will be interesting how they interpret tonight's numbers to see how -- and they look at the polls for next week because if there is a genuine sense that Mitt Romney can't close the deal people are going to start getting nervous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington", "Idaho", "Alaska"]}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RBR", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "What is your realistic aspiration for the 10 states?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, we're working harder in, you know, a few of the states like, you know, Washington and Idaho and Alaska, and a couple others, but realistically I don't have a number.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "I mean, are you and Mitt Romney in bed together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJS", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "If you were Barack Obama and you're watching your attack ad just now for example, who is best served to the conservatives to take on Barack Obama -- the hypocrite, the fake or the flip flopper?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJS", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Well, I think the people that are helped at best are the voters to find out whom they're voting for, if they're voting for somebody who says I am the conservative and he's a really a fake, you know, people need to know that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "What did you make of it all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Well, I can't interpret all that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "On the assumption at the moment that Mitt Romney may end up being the nominee, would you serve under him if he asked you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, it depends on -- he is not likely to do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Would you feel comfortable with Ahmadinejad having a nuclear weapon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "I wouldn't want that to happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ahmadinejad"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "-- and why they would be so anxious about him having a nuclear weapon capability?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "NNS", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Did you agree with the Senate's decision to not allow any exemptions to Obama's birth control rule?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Well, I want the government in insurance, this whole idea that the government can tell the insurance company what they should give and people now when you're talking about mandating, you know, birth control pills in an insurance program, that's no longer insurance.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "What was it about him you think will be his legacy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Andrew was full of passion, exuberance, fearlessness and often coming up with statements that he couldn't prove, although he was also obsessed with facts and wanting to ferret out facts and the truth so there are all these paradoxes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "What was the guy that you knew?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Andrew was -- he could be polarizing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Did you know if he was having health issues?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "I know that there were some health concerns.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "What will your lasting memory be of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Oh, gosh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "So I think if he had been here talking about himself under these circumstances, Andrew would have been pretty scathing about part of his character, wouldn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "He would.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andrew"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2012"]}, "docId": "120301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ":", "NNP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "CD", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "How do you think he's doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Well, I'm excited to be -- Buzzfeed is where it's at for 2012, for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]